Rook secures construction milestone payments.
In a renovation project, the client wants protection against paying too early, while the artisan needs reliable payment once the work is accepted.
Kitchen renovation, Phase 1: 3,000 USDC total, 2,850 USDC released today, and 150 USDC protected as retention.
Rook checks the evidence: client acceptance, invoice, compliance, no dispute, and completion photos.
Then a deterministic payment policy decides whether the release is safe to execute.
The approved release has already been executed through KeeperHub on Sepolia with simulation, broadcast, and an authoritative audit trail.
The live proof shows the execution ID, transaction hash, gas used, timestamp, audit status, and explorer link.
When client acceptance is missing, Rook safely blocks the payment before execution.
Rook pays when evidence is complete, protects retention, and records every KeeperHub execution.
Rook. Secure milestone payments for construction. Executed through KeeperHub.